how is your new job going to be honest I can't complain
كيف ستكون وظيفتك الجديدة صادقة لا يمكنني الشكوى
complain I really love the company that I am working for
شكوى أنا حقا أحب الشركة التي أعمل من أجلها
my co-workers are all really friendly and helpful
زملائي في العمل كلهم ​​ودودون ومفيدون حقًا
they really help me feel welcome it's a really energetic
إنهم يساعدونني حقًا في الشعور بالترحيب ، إنه نشط حقًا
energetic and fun atmosphere my boss is hilarious
الجو النشط والممتع مديري فرحان
and he's really flexible really
وهو مرن حقًا حقًا
how so he allows me to come in when I want
كيف يسمح لي بالحضور عندما أريد
find and make my own hours I can also leave early if
ابحث عن ساعتي الخاصة وأخذها ، يمكنني أيضًا المغادرة مبكرًا إذا
early if I start early there is no real dress code either
في وقت مبكر إذا بدأت مبكرًا ، فلا يوجد قواعد لباس حقيقية أيضًا
I can wear jeans and a T-shirt if I want I can even
يمكنني ارتداء الجينز وقميصًا إذا أردت أن أتمكن من ذلك
I can even wear shorts in the summer wow it sounds
يمكنني حتى ارتداء السراويل القصيرة في الصيف واو ، يبدو الأمر
sounds really cool I can't stand wearing a suit every day
يبدو رائعًا حقًا لا أستطيع الوقوف وهو يرتدي بدلة كل يوم
everyday which do you prefer working late or finishing
كل يوم ما تفضل العمل متأخرا أو الانتهاء
finishing early I prefer finishing early I really enjoyed
الانتهاء في وقت مبكر أفضل الانتهاء في وقت مبكر استمتعت حقا
really enjoy the morning I love getting up early and going for a run
استمتع حقًا في الصباح الذي أحب الاستيقاظ مبكرًا والذهاب للجري
for a run there's nothing like watching the sunrise while drinking my morning
للجري لا يوجد شيء مثل مشاهدة شروق الشمس أثناء شرب صباحي
my morning coffee really I am opposite
قهوتي الصباحية حقًا أنا معاكس
opposite I love sleeping in I am
مقابل أنا أحب النوم في أنا
I am most alert in the evenings I'm a real night owl
أنا في حالة تأهب قصوى في المساء أنا بومة ليلية حقيقية
well you know what they
حسنا أنت تعرف ماذا هم
do you know what they say the early bird catches the worm you know
هل تعرف ما يقولونه إن الطائر المبكر يمسك الدودة التي تعرفها
you know you could be right maybe I will try to go to bed a
أنت تعلم أنك قد تكون على حق ، ربما سأحاول الذهاب إلى الفراش
bed a little earlier tonight
فراش في وقت مبكر بقليل الليلة